My name is Sakura Kawasaki. I have compiled a brief report on the behind-the-scenes of the World Figure Championships, for which I served as a special supporter. Please have a look.
I'm so nervous, but we had time to practice in the morning, and it was the first time for the three of us to practice together.
I'm nervous, but I think I have to smile at every ceremony, so I'll do my best.
I will do my best.
Thank you very much for watching.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
I was really nervous.
I was really nervous, but my fans came to the show so much.
Their support gave me so much strength.
Everyone in the venue clapped so much.
They welcomed me so warmly.
I was able to enjoy skating!
I spun a little bit in practice.
I hit my butt really hard in practice
I'm in a lot of pain right now.
I'm going to take over and scrub for 2 minutes.
I'm going to take over from now and scrub for 2 minutes.
LESSO there.
I think it's like a repetition of "going down" and "going up".
I think it's coming out.
It is taking off.
Yes, sir.
Today, on the second day of the convention, the best room in the world was decided with only a few people!
Oh, my God.
Oh, God, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Today, on the second day of the competition, with only a few people in the room, the world's best pair of...
Oh, no!
World what?
The world of pairs.
World of pairs
World of Pairs
Can we do it again?
Let's do it again.
This is Marimini on the quadruple axeler.
It's the first day of the competition, and we have been watching the videos from the first day, and we have been watching Mengi as well, but there is a big difference between the video and the live performance.
Especially in Ice Dance, I felt the power of the pairs,
Today was the women's free skate, and the audience was really enthusiastic,
Everyone brought Japanese Pocky towels, and it was really warm, just like Nogizaka's live,
I was really happy to have been able to see them live today.
Today was the last day of the event!
I will do my best on the last day, cheerfully and happily!
This is my third year as a Kanki fan!
I also rode the rhythm dance of Tonadairumi live yesterday.
I was really impressed because I couldn't help but do it!
Amazing!
One revolution at a time, poof!
Go, go, go!!!
I'm pretty sure I could have won.
Go for it!
Yes!
We made it through the four days without a hitch. Thank you very much.
It was such a valuable experience, and I don't think I've ever had the chance to do anything like this.
I'm really grateful for the opportunity, and since it was my first experience, I'd like to make the most of it.
I would like to make the most of this experience and use it in my activities at Akizaka!
Thank you very much for the 4 days. Bye bye!